[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How was the FIFA World Cup Won in 2006?", "correct_answer": "penalty kick shootout", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "The winner was decided by the end of the regular time.", "One team won in overtime."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1996 movie received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "Striptease", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed", "Barb Wire", "The Island of Dr. Moreau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Jewish New Year called?", "correct_answer": "Rosh Ha-Shanah", "incorrect_answers": ["Yom Kippur", "Shabbat", "Hanukkah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian manufacturer of sports cars was founded in 1929, and in 1947 it started producing street-legal vehicles.", "correct_answer": "Ferrari", "incorrect_answers": ["Maserati", "None of these", "Lamborghini"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hardees medium sized Strawberry Shake (Hand-dipped) is higher in fats and total calories than Wendys medium sized Frosty Dairy Dessert.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Copenhagen meet Marengo?", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Sherwood Forrest", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These actors both portrayed Vito Corleone in The Godfather trilogy, and won Academy Awards for their performances.", "correct_answer": "Marlon Brando and Robert De Niro", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Buscemi and Harvey Keitel", "Joe Pesci and Ray Liotta", "John Belushi and Dan Aykroyd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed Return of the Magnificent Seven, the first sequel to The Magnificent Seven?", "correct_answer": "Burt Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry Cohen", "Ted Richmond", "Elmer Bernstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scallops live a sedentary live and never move around.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Almost everyone knows of Hank Aaron, Babe Ruth, Sandy Koufax, Bob Gibson, and Ichiro Suzuki but who was Bill Klem?", "correct_answer": "The Father of Modern Umpires", "incorrect_answers": ["The first professional baseball player", "The man who replaced Lou Gehrig at first base for the Yankees.", "The man who sold Babe Ruth to the Yankees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stegosaurus had a brain about the size of an orange.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What work brought Rose Sayer, a character from the movie, The African Queen, to Africa?", "correct_answer": "Missionary", "incorrect_answers": ["Cartography", "Research", "Exploration"]}]